Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
Hi, I'm Mark Kerr
and I'm representing
American freestyle wrestling,
and I'm here
at the World Vale Tudo 3
to prove that it's
the best fighting style.
ANNOUNCER: And that is
wrestler, Mark Kerr.
6'1'', 260 pounds
from Toledo, Ohio,
and again, his specialty
is freestyle wrestling
and this is
his first professional fight.
This guy, we expect
a lot out of this guy,
'cause his cornerman,
Richard Hamilton,
who brought in three
of the strongest Americans
to ever step into this ring,
that would be Dan Severn,
Don Frye, and Mark Coleman.
He told us earlier today that
this guy is the best
he has ever seen.
And as he enters the ring
for the first time
in his professional career,
we will see how he holds up
to some of the toughest
competition.
And now coming in
is the biggest here.
Paul Varelans,
6'8", 330 pounds.
From San Jose, California.
And he's had eight years
of wrestling experience too,
but he's definitely
more skilled on his feet.
And there is Sergio Batarelli
getting the fighters ready
-as we await the opening bell.
-(BELL RINGING)
And this fight is underway!
And Kerr is going at him.
He is trying to take him down.
Can he take him down?
Oh! A massive takedown
on Varelans.
A double leg takedown by Kerr.
Look at him jockey
for position.
Wrestling skills
on full display and...
Oh! A knee to the face!
Wow! A magnificent knee
to the face
and another knee to the face.
I'll tell you what.
Varelans is one tough kid,
but he's taking
some brutal shots
to the face here.
His face is getting
destroyed right now.
Batarelli is watching on.
He has...
Yes, he has stopped the fight.
-It is over.
-(BELL RINGING)
ANNOUNCER:
And Kerr wins his debut.
That's right. Varelans was
unable to stop the fight.
Batarelli had to step in.
Whoa. Look at that.
Some serious cuts there.
(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
-Is he fine?
-(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Okay. Take your time.
Take your time.
Come on. I got you.
Come sit down.
SERGIO: TKO. Ref stop.
CORNERMAN: There you go.
Do you know who you are?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
In a fight.
CORNERMAN: Yes, you was
in a fight. How did it go?
-You know what happened?
-PAUL: I... lost.
Can I ask him
if he's going to be okay?
I just wanna know.
He'll be fine, Mark.
He'll be fine.
Back to your corner.
(CROWD CHEERING)
-SERGIO: Folks, we ready?
-Just five seconds, please.
(CROWD CHEERING)
INTERVIEWER 1: And what are
you thinking
at the beginning
of the fight?
MARK: You know, the...
the second that bell rings,
you can just look
at some people
and you can just tell
that... that they're
scared to death.
I mean, you can see
in their eyes.
You can even smell it
in their sweat.
INTERVIEWER 1: Wow.
MARK: But you know,
it isn't until the first time
I can put my hands on them,
and really assert myself
on the other person
that you can really feel,
like almost instantly,
if the person is going to
give in or not.
INTERVIEWER 1:
So, what happens next?
MARK: It's simple.
Am I going to hurt him
before he hurts me?
And if he happens to hurt me,
then I am gonna hurt him
two times as bad.
(INTERVIEWER 1 CHUCKLES)
MARK: 'Cause,
let me tell you something,
when you get punched
in the face,
you can have two reactions.
You can either cower away,
or you can want to punish
the person for punching you.
But I developed a third way.
You know, if I get kicked
or if I get punched,
I'm going to
something different
-than punish you.
-(INTERVIEWER 1 CHUCKLES)
I'm going to physically
impose my will on to you.
And you... you really feel
when that happens,
when the person just lets go,
and he totally withers away
in your arms.
And that's...
That's a pretty
powerful thing.
It is crazy
because in the beginning,
I was just kind of having fun.
I was operating
on this animal instinct that
just took over.
Uh, I'm gonna try
and explain it,
and maybe in this way,
but it's... it's kind of
strange, you know?
The whole thing felt
very evolutionary.
I mean, I wrestled in college,
but... but this is
something totally different.
INTERVIEWER 1:
Well, what do you mean?
MARK: Like the moment I felt
that rush, that first hit,
I realized I was getting
pretty close to
something that's...
It's almost magical.
INTERVIEWER 1: Wow.
MARK: You get to the point
where you have to
ask yourself,
like, would you stick
your finger
in your opponent's cut?
Spread it out
a little bit more?
Just... Just to win?
To make him feel pain?
Would you?
INTERVIEWER 1: I mean,
I guess I would.
MARK: (CHUCKLING)
Of course you would.
You know why?
Because winning is
the best feeling there is.
INTERVIEWER 1: Yeah.
MARK: And keep in mind,
this was a tournament
down in Brazil.
So if you won,
you didn't go home.
No. You went on
and you fought the next guy,
and then the next guy
right after that,
and then the next guy,
and then the next guy.
So, by the end,
you felt like a god.
INTERVIEWER 1: Sounds amazing.
-It's incredible.
-(MARK CHUCKLES)
Honestly, when you win,
nothing else
in this world matters.
And it kind of might be
the best feeling
-in the world, you know?
-INTERVIEWER 1: Yeah.
MARK: And it's a feeling
I didn't even know
was possible.
I mean, fuck, man,
I'm getting chills right now
just... just telling you
about this.
Uh, so, Moti...
Uh, The Hammer.
Yeah.
He has experience
in the Octagon.
Uh, you don't.
He's tough. Super tough.
What is it that you think
you're gonna bring
to this fight?
Well, I think that
I feel really good
about my cardiovascular level.
I feel great about my power,
which I've improved on.
(INHALES)
But you know what,
it's like the difference
between a flashlight
and a laser beam.
Wow.
That's awesome.
What do you mean by that?
I have to make sure that
I'm a 100% concentrated
on what I have to do.
Because if not,
then my emotions
will be running
around everywhere,
like a flashlight. (CHUCKLING)
Yeah, that makes
sense, actually.
MARK: Yeah. I mean,
think about it.
It applies to you
and everybody else
-in this room.
-INTERVIEWER 1: Sure.
If we don't control
our emotions,
our fears and our anxieties
will get the best of us.
And you know what happens?
We get slapped around
by our emotions... (CHUCKLES)
-...and we can't have that.
-INTERVIEWER 1: That's right.
-Right?
-COLEMAN: Hey, Kerr.
Get your ass up.
They're all waiting, buddy.
INTERVIEWER 1:
Hey, thank you so much
-for your time.
-Yeah. Thank you very much.
-I appreciate it.
-I appreciate you.
-Ready? Good to see you.
-My man.
-Hey, the only difference...
-Yeah.
...is the shape of the ring,
all right?
-A cage.
-(CHUCKLES) It's a cage.
I know. I know.
First time in the Octagon.
INTERVIEWER 1: I was
telling him the same thing.
-Right.
-Yo, guys, come on.
There's only been
14 of these fucking things.
-He's a killer.
-INTERVIEWER 2: Excuse me.
-Coleman?
-COLEMAN: Yeah, yeah.
INTERVIEWER 2:
Vidmark Entertainment.
Can I ask about your plans
to take on Bobish?
-Oh, Bobish. Um... Kerr?
-MARK: Yeah?
-COLEMAN: Get him down early.
-You got it.
-I'm gonna go warm up.
-COLEMAN: All right.
Sorry. Where was I?
Uh, you were
talking about Bobish.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING IN DISTANCE)
COMMENTATOR 1: And now
we get to the big boys.
Mark Kerr making his debut
against Moti Horenstein,
who is making his
second appearance
in the Octagon losing
only to Mark Coleman.
And here comes
255-pound, Mark Kerr,
a former Division 1
NCAA champion
at Syracuse University.
ANNOUNCER 1:
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time for the big men,
as we begin
our heavyweight tournaments.
Standing to my left,
he's the winner of
the 1994 World Cup
Wrestling Championship,
the winner of
the Men's Freestyle National
Championship,
an NCAA Division 1 champion,
he stands 6'1",
-and weighs in at 255 pounds.
-(CROWD CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER 1: He's fighting out
of Phoenix, Arizona,
please welcome
in his Octagon debut,
Mark Kerr!
Hi.
Probably looking at my eyes.
-How did that happen?
-(CHUCKLING)
Well, have you ever heard of
the Ultimate
Fighting Championship?
The UFC?
They were kind of like
the first in combat sports.
Is that boxing?
Well, there's
a little boxing in it. Yeah.
It's more like martial arts
that have been around
for thousands of years
and we bring them all together
to see which one is the best.
So, I come
from a wrestling background,
but I might fight a guy
who comes
from a karate background
or a guy who comes
from a boxing background
-as well.
-Yeah, I've heard about this.
That's the bloody thing
they're trying to ban.
(CHUCKLING) Yes, that's right.
That's right, it is.
But I gotta tell you,
the popularity of the sport
comes from the stereotype
that you're gonna see
the bloodiest
and the goriest sport
-you've ever seen.
-Yeah, I can't do that.
It... it bothers me.
And it should bother
a lot of people.
Do you hate each other
when you fight?
Absolutely not.
PEGGY: Oh.
MARK: Absolutely not. No.
NURSE: Uh, sorry to interrupt.
Uh, Dr. Cortez
can see you now.
Great. Thank you so much.
It was great to talk to you.
Thank you. It was great
to talk with you, too.
(MARK CLEARS THROAT)
Here.
What's up, little man?
-I'm sorry. He's kind of shy.
-MARK: That's okay.
But I think he wants
your autograph.
MARK: Sure, no problem.
Wh... What's your name?
(CHUCKLES) His name is Cosmo.
But could you make it out
to his brother, Murray, too?
Sure.
(SOFTLY) Cosmo.
No fighting.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
-(MARK GROANS)
-DR. CORTEZ: Hey, Mark.
-Hey, Raja.
-How's it going?
How are you, man?
Great. You must be
a little jet-lagged.
Yeah. Just flew
in this morning.
-Where'd you come from again?
-Japan.
So UFC is now in Japan?
No, it's kind of like
an NBA, ABA situation.
Two different leagues.
This one's called Pride.
Well, why don't you
take off your shirt.
Let me take a look.
RECEPTIONIST: Okay,
so we're doing the usual?
Sending your scripts
over to Safeway?
You know what
I'm thinking this month?
I'm gonna switch
over to A to Z.
They handle
my insurance much better.
Let's do that. Yeah.
Okay. Sure. Yeah.
That's no problem.
I can switch
the insurance over.
-And they'll probably...
-You know what?
Let's not even deal
with the insurance.
You know how they are
over at Safeway.
They're just a pain
in the butt, so...
Plus it's easier for you.
I'll just pay out of pocket.
Are you sure? Some of these
are going to be expensive.
Yeah, no, not a problem.
I don't get punched
-in the face for nothing...
-(RECEPTIONIST CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I'll pay out of pocket.
Not a problem.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING
OVER TV)
Honey!
-Hi. Uh, thank you.
-I made this for you.
-Love you.
-Mmm.
Do you want me to
throw this out
or are you going to have this?
You used the skim milk, right?
Yeah, skim milk
like last week.
I switched to
whole milk last week.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-I thought I told you.
I know, but you gotta tell me
these things.
I'm gonna get it wrong
if you don't
tell me these things.
It's all right.
I'll just make another one.
DAWN: Sneakers. (SMACKS LIPS)
Hi, my love.
MARK: How much banana
did you put in?
-DAWN: Half a banana.
-Half?
You changed that, too?
What is it now?
It's actually one and a half.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING
OVER TV CONTINUES)
You're good.
So good, baby girl.
-Oh, come on.
-Come on, what?
I said not on the couch.
How many times
do I say not on the couch?
-She just wants a belly rub.
-She's destroyed the couch.
This is expensive.
She's just a good baby girl.
(SNEAKERS MEOWING)
All right. Come on.
-Oh, Mark.
-Come on, come on, come on.
-You destroyed enough.
-(CAT HISSES)
-I know.
-DAWN: See?
MARK: Hey,
she tried to bite me.
-It's okay.
-Oh, come on, Mark. (CHUCKLES)
MARK: Oh,
she sounds like her mama.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Come on, let her back up.
She can sit on me
and she'll be fine.
-Come here, baby.
-(SIGHS)
(SMACKS LIPS) Come see Mama.
Mmm, my baby.
(TUTS) Yeah, baby. Hi.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING
CONTINUES ON TV)
Hey, it was really nice of you
to make my smoothie.
-I really...
-Mmm-hmm.
-I... (CHUCKLES) I mean it.
-Thank you.
-Shut your mouth.
No, I mean it. Thank you.
Even though it was made
with the wrong milk,
you didn't know.
-But thank you.
-(KISSES)
-How's that feel?
-MARK: It feels great.
Do you want some more?
-(LAUGHS)
-Should you ask like that?
Yes, you can
stretch me more. Yes.
-Too much?
-Never.
-No.
-Too much?
-Tell me.
-No.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
-(GRUNTING)
-Come on, baby.
(TAKE ME IN YOUR ARMS
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
(SONG FADES OUT)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
One Mississippi,
two Mississippi,
three Mississippi,
four Mississippi,
five Mississippi...
(SIGHS)
(TAKE ME IN YOUR ARMS
PLAYING SOFTLY)
(WHEN I DREAM PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
-Excuse me.
-Yes.
I'm sorry. Would you mind
opening the shade?
-I'd love to see the sunset.
-MAN: Okay. Sure.
(SONG FADES OUT)
MARK: Um...
The contract says...
The past contract
says $3,300...
-Okay.
-It say remaining.
Remaining. Yes.
Remaining. So...
$3,300 still remaining
come to me.
So, one month no contract?
No money? No more? This is it?
Yes, no contract anymore.
No money. That's it.
Am I speaking too fast?
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(MARK CHUCKLING)
(IN ENGLISH) Maybe
my English too fast.
Um, I'm going to
need more money.
But we have to
discuss about this.
-We have to discuss. Yes.
-OFFICIAL: No, no, not you.
I talk to my headquarters.
Not you.
You're going to speak
to your headquarters.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
It's okay?
I... I understand that,
but before I fight again,
we should...
we should clear this up.
We should have
an understanding.
an agreement, yes?
-Before I fight again.
-(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
-Yes. Okay.
-OFFICIAL: Just wait.
-It's fair.
-It's okay?
-Arigato.
Yes.
(PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING)
-COLEMAN: Kerr.
-(CHUCKLES) Coleman.
-You're an animal.
-You good?
Anything good out there?
Nope, I'm already back, buddy.
-Good?
-REPORTER 1: Yep.
Um, so, how do you know
Mark Kerr?
Oh, Kerr and I go way back.
You know, we wrestled
each other back in '88,
you know, and, uh...
So, way back then
I knew who Mark Kerr was.
You know, we competed
against each other,
-but he's a buddy of mine.
-Oh, so...
Who started
the professional first?
I guess I did because I was
a couple years ahead of him.
Kind of got into that
fighting game prior to him.
He got in, I was trained
to help him out.
I was actually his,
uh, first kind of
trainer and manager.
-Oh, okay.
-Yeah. It was fun times,
but, you know,
now we train together
and he's come into his own.
I mean,
look what he's been doing.
I'm super proud of him.
And, yeah,
I couldn't be more proud.
SHOPKEEPER: Which one
would you like to see?
MARK: The bowl, please.
With the gold.
SHOPKEEPER: There you are.
Wow.
SHOPKEEPER: Yes.
It is so artistic
and very expensive.
It's beautiful.
(SHOPKEEPER SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(IN ENGLISH) I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
I don't speak Japanese.
What did you say?
Um...
You have a good eye.
Ah! Thank you.
I'll take it.
(SHOPKEEPER SPEAKING JAPANESE)
MARK: Arigato.
(IN ENGLISH) You know what?
I'll take this too, please.
SHOPKEEPER: Oh, beautiful.
It's for my girlfriend.
She loves colors.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Arigato.
REPORTER 2: (IN ENGLISH)
So, let's talk about
your fight.
What do you think
about your opponent,
Igor Vovchanchyn?
He's a very famous fighter
for having a hard punch.
He has a hard punch.
Um, it's probably gonna be
my toughest fight...
because of his experience.
But I have to fight
a clean fight.
I have to fight
a very technical fight
if I'm gonna be victorious.
But we as a human,
sometimes we lose.
What you think
that would feel like?
Can you imagine that?
You know, I try not to let
thoughts like that
enter my mind.
But if they do...
I really wouldn't know
what to do with them,
because I... I don't know
what that's like. (CHUCKLES)
I've never lost a fight.
I'm sorry,
but that's the truth.
But can I ask you
one more time?
I've got to ask you,
as a journalist.
Hypothetically speaking,
if... if I lost...
I don't know how to
even respond to that
because I've never lost.
Yeah. Thank you.
I mean, I'm trying to
intellectualize it with you,
but I just...
Yeah, I can't. (SIGHS)
We apologize
if we kept you waiting.
We would like to start
with the following
rule changes.
The following actions
are now deemed to be illegal.
Number one, biting.
(TRANSLATOR SPEAKING JAPANESE)
PRIDE DIRECTOR: (IN ENGLISH)
Number two, eye gouging.
(TRANSLATOR SPEAKING JAPANESE)
PRIDE DIRECTOR: (IN ENGLISH)
Number three, headbutting.
-(TRANSLATING IN JAPANESE)
-(IN ENGLISH) And now...
In this position,
knee and kick
to the face are faults.
(SPEAKING UKRAINIAN)
(CROWD MURMURING)
(IN ENGLISH) I'm sorry.
I would just like to make sure
that we understood correctly.
If the opponent is
in the position
while his...
His face is upward,
is it allowed for
the person standing
to kick in the face?
Yes. That is okay.
Thank you.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT:
Excuse me, miss.
I'm gonna have to ask you
close your tray table
as the pilot has
started his descent.
-Yeah, sure.
-FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Thank you.
(INDISTINCT
ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA)
(ANNOUNCEMENT CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
-(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
-(STEAM HISSING)
COLEMAN: Just be
patient out there.
Have fun.
Don't get in
a kickboxing match with him.
Be patient. Find your time.
-Get him down. Do your thing.
-MARK: Yeah.
You're gonna
have fun out there.
-(KNOCK ON DOOR, OPENS)
-MARK: Fun.
DAWN: Guess who it is.
-Hey, Dawn.
-DAWN: Hi.
-(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
-(DOOR CLOSES)
(MAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON TV)
-DAWN: Oh, I'm sorry.
-Let me grab this from...
DAWN: Okay.
All right, buddy. I'm thinking
like five to ten, all right?
Yep.
(GRUNTS)
-Okay.
-(MARK GRUNTS)
Hi.
Wanna come sit, baby?
Are you okay?
Are you high?
-Look at me.
-(MARK SIGHS)
Look at me.
Are you... (CHUCKLES)
Why are you being so weird?
Your eyes look weird. Look--
Okay.
Come here.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
You make me feel
so fucking stupid
coming in here.
It's like you guys were
talking shit or something.
I fucking flew halfway
across the globe.
-You asked me to come.
-I said thank you.
Oh, yeah?
And then you acted like
a fucking dick
in front of your friend.
Don't call me next time.
"Please, Dawn, come.
I'm lonely." Fuck you!
I'm trying to focus.
It has nothing to do with you.
Can you say hello to me?
Dawn, it has nothing
to do with you.
You don't even have time
to say hello to me?
I just don't wanna fight.
Not now. Please.
Would it be easier
if I punched you in the face?
Yes, punch me
in the fucking face.
Yeah? Could we
communicate then?
Punch me in the fucking face.
Biggest night of my life.
-Come in.
-(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(IN ENGLISH) I'm so sorry.
We are ready
for you downstairs.
Please, just come with me.
Yeah. Thank you.
You're out of fucking control.
I'm sorry.
(INDISTINCT
ELEVATOR ANNOUNCEMENT)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
STEPHEN QUADROS: This is
a true clash of two giants
in the sport, Bas.
BAS: Uh, I really don't know
what to expect here.
Of course we expect
Igor to start pouring bombs
on Mark to go
for the takedown.
STEPHEN QUADROS:
We've got Kerr,
the quintessential wrestler,
the takedown artist,
against maybe
the purest puncher
in the game, Igor Vovchanchyn.
And there's Mark Coleman,
a former three-time
UFC champion,
uh, cornering Mark Kerr.
So, you know, he's gonna be...
I'm gonna go
find my seat, okay.
ANNOUNCER: Mark Kerr!
BAS: On paper,
I would say Mark Kerr's
going to win the fight.
STEPHEN QUADROS:
I would say it too,
but Vovchanchyn may have faced
a tougher caliber opponent
than Kerr has.
BAS: Yeah, that's what
most people say, but if...
But I'll tell you one thing.
Vovchanchyn has never faced
a Mark Kerr,
but let's be fair.
On the other side of the coin,
Kerr has never faced
a striker, possibly,
as dangerous as
Igor Vovchanchyn.
STEPHEN QUADROS: This is
a monumental battle here.
-(DRUMS BEATING)
-(CROWD CHEERING)
COLEMAN: Let's go, Kerr.
(REFEREE SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(COLEMAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCT INSTRUCTIONS)
-(BELL RINGS)
-(CROWD CHEERING)
COLEMAN: Move! Move!
Legs! Legs!
(IGOR'S CORNERMAN
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
COLEMAN: Pressure.
Lock his hands, Kerr.
Come on, Mark! Let's go, baby!
Play smart!
There we go.
(ALL EXCLAIM)
COLEMAN: Under takedown!
-Get it!
-(MAN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
Let's go!
Use your hands.
There we go! Pull! Pull!
-Keep him down.
-Come on, Mark!
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
COLEMAN: Come on.
(UKRAINIAN CORNERMAN
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
COLEMAN: There we go.
-Get up!
-Get up, Mark! Get up!
COLEMAN: Get up! Hands up!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Go! Keep going! Keep going!
Nice! Nice!
Get him! Get him!
He's got your head, Mark.
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Detach yourself, buddy!
Get up right now!
(JARRING MUSIC PLAYING)
You gotta get up right now!
Get up, Mark! Come on!
Move, buddy! You got to move!
Protect yourself, buddy!
Get up! Move right now!
Kerr, move!
Come on.
-Get up, Kerr!
-(MARK GROANS)
You gotta go!
You gotta get up!
(REFEREE
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
STEPHEN QUADROS:
And Kerr is out!
BAS: Oh, my God!
STEPHEN QUADROS:
Kerr has been knocked out
by Igor Vovchanchyn!
On his knees, but... but wait.
Vovchanchyn is wild
in celebration.
He slayed the beast.
MARK: How is that not illegal?
How is that not illegal?
How is that not illegal on top
of my head?
-It's illegal.
-(APOLOGIZING IN JAPANESE)
No, no, no.
STEPHEN QUADROS: Oh,
you know what it was?
BAS: I think it was a foul.
There are no knees
allowed on the ground.
He's no force.
STEPHEN QUADROS: That's right.
That's right. There are
no knees allowed to the head
when an opponent is all but...
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
It's okay, baby.
STEPHEN QUADROS:
The referee has raised
Igor Vovchanchyn's arm
in victory.
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SAKAKIBARA SPEAKING JAPANESE)
-(IN ENGLISH) Mr. Sakakibara?
-SAKAKIBARA: Yes?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
How are you?
I am fine. And you?
I'm not good. I'm not good.
Bad referee.
Bad... Vovchanchyn bam
on top of the head.
It's wrong. Foul.
Referee no call foul.
And then twice,
two more times,
bam on top of my head.
And I was laying
on the ground waiting
for the referee
to call a foul.
He didn't call foul. (PANTING)
It's wrong. It's illegal
on top of the head. Bam.
-Okay. Okay. I talk to him.
-Twice.
-Please. Please.
-Okay? Yeah, okay.
Arigato.
-I didn't lose.
-Yeah.
(SAKAKIBARA SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(MARK SNIFFLES)
(ELEVATOR DINGING)
(INDISTINCT ELEVATOR
ANNOUNCEMENT)
(SOBBING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
COLEMAN: You've got
some bumps and bruises.
You're not injured.
You'll heal up
in a week or two, tops.
Okay?
(CLEARS THROAT) Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
I'll heal up in a week
or two, tops.
(SNIFFLES) I mean,
my hands aren't broken.
-My... my feet are fine.
-COLEMAN: Mmm-hmm.
(INHALES) My head's
a little banged up.
Igor is one tough
motherfucker, huh?
MARK: Tough motherfucker.
COLEMAN: I'll give him that.
(MARK CHUCKLING)
Yeah.
Thank you.
COLEMAN: All right, guys,
I'm gonna run outside.
-I'll be back, okay?
-MARK: Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Coleman,
um, can I just talk to you?
-Yeah.
-Sorry. I just want to know
if he... if he's
gonna be okay.
I've never seen him
like this before, so...
-He should be fine.
-Okay.
And he seemed okay, right?
Yeah, I mean, I just...
I don't know. I, like, knew it
before he stepped in the ring
and he just...
What do you mean?
Well, he just wasn't serious,
I think, and...
About the fight.
Like the past two weeks
we've been out drinking
and stuff and partying and...
-You never brought that up?
-To you?
-To me, yeah.
-Why?
He doesn't need to be drinking
two weeks before a fight.
I'm not his trainer,
and I'm not a fighter.
And... And he seemed
fine about it.
He seemed fine.
And I don't know
if he ever thought
this was possible,
that he would lose.
And I didn't think
it was possible.
Hmm. All right. I get it.
-Just be there for him. Okay?
-DAWN: Yeah.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(MARK SIGHS)
(SAKAKIBARA SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(CONTINUES IN JAPANESE)
(IN ENGLISH) We have decided
to call this fight
with Igor no contest.
No contest.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(IN ENGLISH) We would be
very happy to have you back
at Pride again.
-Thank you.
-Arigato.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(IN ENGLISH) Thank you.
What'd they say?
They decided
to call it a no contest.
That's awesome.
Why are you still so sad?
Because Dawn... I'm not sad.
It's just I don't do that
for no contest.
-Mmm-hmm.
-I want the decision.
-You know?
I mean, it's just
I'm out there.
I'm sacrificing everything,
literally, you know.
-Mmm-hmm. I see it.
-I'm sacrificing everything
-out there...
-Yeah, it's very heavy.
-...for the reward at the end.
-Right.
It's... the high
from that thing that I do.
The thing that
I just did out there.
It's a high that...
There's no other high
like it in the world.
I can only imagine.
I... Yeah, I can see it.
I can see it in you
when you're doing it,
-you know?
-It's 40,000 people...
-Yeah.
-...in there cheering you on.
I mean, that's orgasmic.
Yeah, I know... (CHUCKLES)
Dawn, I'm not kidding.
I'm not kidding. It's...
I'm talking about
the highest of highs.
-Mmm-hmm.
-And two men out there
competing against each other.
And it's only us
and it's so raw.
-But you...
-That competition is crazy.
...got to have
the competition...
And you had that
feeling, you fought.
You had that feeling
but you don't seem...
you don't seem happy about it.
No. I'm trying to
explain it to you,
-but you just keep talking.
-Yeah.
You just keep talking over me.
No, I'm trying to understand
what you're saying
and I'm trying to
support you.
I know, but only
because I'm trying to
tell you exactly
what happened.
-IGOR: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-(MARK CHUCKLES)
-Hey, brother!
-IGOR: How you doing?
-MARK: How are you? Oh.
-IGOR: Ow!
MARK: Oh, you okay?
Gosh, I'm sorry.
-Is that from me?
-(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Let me see. Can I see?
(TRANSLATOR SPEAKING
UKRAINIAN)
(IGOR GRUNTS)
-Nice. How many stitches?
-(IGOR SPEAKING UKRAINIAN)
TRANSLATOR: (IN ENGLISH) Four.
-MARK: Four stitches.
-Four. Four.
(CHUCKLES)
Does the body feel okay?
(IGOR SPEAKING UKRAINIAN)
TRANSLATOR: (IN ENGLISH)
A little bit of the knee.
-A little bit of the knee.
-IGOR: Yeah.
You know why?
A lot of my head.
(TRANSLATOR SPEAKING
UKRAINIAN)
-(IGOR SPEAKING UKRAINIAN)
-(MARK CHUCKLES)
-I'm sorry.
-No, no, no, it's okay.
Ah! It's totally okay.
Tell him it's natural.
A natural reaction.
(TRANSLATOR SPEAKING
UKRAINIAN)
My head was down there.
My face is down there.
(TRANSLATOR SPEAKING
UKRAINIAN)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Let's all get a picture. Yeah?
IGOR: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do it together.
-Let's do it. Yes. Yes.
-IGOR: Of course.
-Can you do a picture?
-Come on!
Let's all get in. Let's all...
Everybody get in.
Hey, Dawn, can you take
this picture for us?
DAWN: Yeah.
MARK: Thank you.
Yeah, come on.
IGOR'S MANAGER:
Look at you two guys.
The best ones.
-Two of the best ones.
-(MARK LAUGHING) That's it.
IGOR: That's it.
(CAMERA SHUTTER
CLICKS, WHIRRS)
-IGOR'S MANAGER: Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Great fight.
-No, this is cold.
-MARK: Cold?
PHARMACIST: Cold.
MARK: Cold and heat?
-This is heat.
-MARK: Heat. Okay.
Thank you. Um, three?
-PHARMACIST: Three, uh...
-Yes.
No, no. Just the one.
-Really? Just one?
-Yeah.
-Just one.
MARK: Okay.
Do you have any,
um, stronger pain medication?
-Pain medication?
-MARK: Yes.
Honey, I don't think they...
I don't think they do that.
No, they do. They've got
everything back there.
Like narcotics, opiates.
No, no, no.
Why not?
Um, you must...
Certification.
-Certification? Yes. Yes.
-Yes. Yes.
-Permission.
-Yes.
-Mark, let's just go.
-It's okay, he has it.
-It's okay. Just take...
take what they have
and we should go.
We have it. Permission.
You get permission for me.
Thank you.
-No, no, it's too late.
-MARK: Yes.
No, no.
What do you have
for me that's strong?
I have Advil. Advil.
-Advil? (CHUCKLES)
-Advil. Yeah, yeah.
-(DAWN CLEARS THROAT)
-Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
-Dawn, would you like some?
-No, no.
They're handing them out
like candy.
Thank you.
You want to hold my hand?
Okay.
MARK: Hey, Joan.
Hey, it's Mark.
Yeah, I'm great.
How you doing?
Great. I'm calling
because I know Dr. Rob
was gonna write that
prescription
for, um, Voltaren for me.
Yeah, but Voltaren
as... as a pill,
it's a little hard
on my tummy.
Yeah, and I know that you guys
can give me the injection,
but you don't wanna
see me in there every day.
(CHUCKLING)
So, what I was hoping is
if Dr. Rob can write
a prescription,
that's a little better
than Voltaren,
um, that's a little stronger,
too, as well.
Yeah. Oh, great. Yeah.
That would be great.
So, whenever he gets back
in the office,
just have him give me a call.
I'll be here.
I... I'm feeling really good.
I appreciate it.
Well, you know,
like a day without pain is
like a day without sunshine.
(CHUCKLING)
(RHYTHM OF MY HEART PLAYING
ON CAR SPEAKERS)
(PARKING BRAKE CRANKS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOFTLY)
Go back to sleep, okay?
MAN: (ON TV)
This solitary clock rotates
six different melodies
on the hour.
As the bell ringer
strikes the rotating...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(UTENSILS CLUNKING)
You're the first bidder...
(INDISTINCT CLAMORING ON TV)
You gotta keep eating, Mark.
Yeah.
-DAWN: You're not gonna get...
-I will.
...any better unless you eat.
-Yeah.
-(FORK CLANKS)
-I know.
-I can't keep coming out
and finding you
like this, Mark. It's just...
What do you mean?
You keep telling me
you're gonna quit
and then I come out and...
Baby, I just need to,
you know...
I just have to get through
this... this moment.
-You know, it's fine.
-What do you want from me?
Do you want me just to pretend
that everything's fine?
No. What do you mean?
That you don't look like this?
I don't look like...
I just want you to be my girl.
That's all. What do you mean?
Look like what? (MUMBLES)
DAWN: You keep telling me
we're going to take a hike.
We are gonna take a hike.
We're going to go today.
You don't even hide it
from me anymore.
I keep going
into the bathroom,
seeing your shit everywhere.
-It's okay.
-It's not okay.
-It's getting bad, Mark.
-No, it's for pain.
-This is getting crazy.
-That's for pain.
-No. No, it's insane.
And you need to get
serious now, okay?
I am serious.
What do you mean?
Because I don't even know
who this person is right now.
I'm ser...
I'm going through this.
What... Going through
the house
looking to find stuff
-just to get me into trouble?
-No.
How about you stop treating me
like a fucking child?
-How about that?
-How about you stop acting
like one, I wouldn't have to.
Like you... You lost a fight.
Big deal. Just get over it.
(MAN ON TV CONTINUES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(BLOWS THUDDING)
(ICE DISPENSER CLICKS)
(ICE CLATTERING)
I just need you to
treat me like a man.
(SNIFFLES)
DAWN: I love you.
You're my big strong man.
I love you.
Okay?
(SOBBING)
COLEMAN: You wanna fight?
I'll take that. Let's go.
(IMITATES YELLING)
You ready?
Okay, let's see what you got.
(IMITATES GRUNTING)
(BABY CRYING)
Looks like I'm winning.
KELLEY: Okay, okay, okay.
The winner is Daddy!
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
Fought a tough opponent.
My toughest yet.
Feels good to be
in the win column again.
And after this payday,
I'm gonna get my girl
-a new playhouse, and a bike.
-(PHONE RINGING)
And... Hold on.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING ON TV)
-(KELLEY SHUSHING)
-Hello.
(DAWN SOBBING ON PHONE)
He's laying on the ground
and he wouldn't wake up
and I couldn't move him and...
-I was like shaking him...
-(WHISPERING) It's Dawn.
-DAWN: ...and he's like...
-She's freaking out.
DAWN: ...took too much
or something. (SOBBING)
Walk me through everything
from the beginning.
I think he did too much
and then I couldn't
wake him up.
I found him on the ground
and then I just was like
shaking him and stuff.
Is he alive?
He's alive, but I didn't know,
you know, at first.
Oh, my fucking God.
Okay. Um...
(DAWN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
I know. Calm down, calm down.
Okay. I need you to
come and help me, okay?
I'm gonna get
on the first flight out.
All right?
I'm going to help you.
I will be there
as soon as I can.
DAWN: I need you to
talk to him.
I got you. I got you.
(DAWN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
I'll see you soon.
First flight.
-DAWN: Okay.
-All right. Bye, Dawn.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
Sorry. Where's
Mark Kerr's room?
Oh. Right down the hall, sir.
COLEMAN: Thank you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
-Coleman.
-COLEMAN: Hey.
(SOFTLY) I know.
-I know, I know.
-(DAWN SOBBING)
-How's he doing?
-DAWN: He just woke up.
He's like in and out
and he's not okay.
-He's awake though?
-DAWN: Yeah.
-You care if I go in?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
COLEMAN: What's
going on, buddy?
-MARK: Hey. (CHUCKLES)
-How are you?
What's up, Coleman?
You're a sight for sore eyes.
Jesus chrimey!
You're looking a little rough.
Not gonna lie.
Oh, man. You should see
the soap in this place, man.
-COLEMAN: Is it bad?
-It's like fucking glue.
-(LAUGHS) Yeah.
-I can kind of see it.
I know, man.
It's doing a number
on my hair, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
-Man, you look good, man.
-Thank you.
So, uh,
what the fuck happened?
-Oh, man.
-You get sick or something?
Yeah. I, um, got sick.
I got sick and it was...
it was pretty unbelievable.
It was pretty bad.
That's the right word.
"It" was bad.
-Mmm-hmm.
-Yeah.
Um...
-So what happened?
Can you give me
the whole story?
Um, I was...
I was on the floor
and... and I couldn't wake up.
And then I, um...
And then Dawn came in
and she was trying to
wake me up
and... she couldn't...
She couldn't wake me up
either and, um...
Um...
You're good.
That's weird.
It's fine.
-Keep going though.
-Yeah, yeah. You know me.
-I don't have verbal pauses.
-I know that. I know that.
Um...
So, then Dawn called the...
She called 911.
And then the ambulance came,
the paramedics came in
and then they couldn't
wake me up either.
And then they put me
in the ambulance
and then they...
I was kind of like
in this weird, altered state.
Like, I was aware of
where I was,
and I could kind of
see things a little blurred,
but I could hear everything.
So my acuity was...
was pretty good.
They were asking me questions,
and... I got a few of
the questions wrong
a little bit.
Like who was the president.
They said,
"Who is the president?"
What'd you say?
Ronald Reagan.
(LAUGHING)
You fucking believe that?
I mean, shit,
you'd say that anyway, right?
I would say that
even on a good day,
I was telling them, like,
"You guys can't ask that."
That's when I realized, like,
that's kind of unfair,
you know, the way they were...
-Hey.
-Yeah.
Listen.
Just stop, all right? Please?
COLEMAN: Hey, you're good.
(MARK SOBBING)
Look. I didn't come out here
because I love Phoenix, dude.
All right?
I came out here
because I want to see you
-get better.
-(MARK SOBBING)
You can't keep doing this
to yourself.
MARK: I know. (SNIFFLES)
-I'm so sorry.
-It's me.
You don't have to
apologize, okay?
I'm one of your best friends
in the world, right?
MARK: Yeah.
COLEMAN: And I'm here
because I love you.
-(SOBBING) I love you, too.
-Okay, come here.
Come here. Come here.
-Yeah.
-I fucking love you, man.
(MARK SOBBING)
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna die.
COLEMAN: Hey, look at me.
You're not gonna die.
All right? Look at me.
I can't. I can't.
We're all in this
together, all right?
There's tons of people
that love you.
But it's got to start
with you, okay?
And you got this.
All right?
All right. I know.
I know. (SNIFFLES)
I know.
Thank you.
(DON'T BE CRUEL
BY BILLY SWAN PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
-That's it?
-PHOTOGRAPHER: Thanks so much.
Thank you for having me today.
COLEMAN: No problem.
I have a little bit
strange question for you.
Okay.
Um, are you okay
to fight without your friend?
-Mark Kerr?
-Yes, Mark Kerr.
Yeah, I've been
worried about him
for quite a while now.
You know, just as a friend.
Yeah, I know your feeling.
I think that loss to Igor,
or whatever you wanna call it,
the no contest.
I think that was
the best thing that
could've happened to him.
I feel like he's going
to come back a better version
of himself, you know.
And I know he wants
to be here.
He loves you guys.
And he's distraught that
he can't make it.
So, what make you
keeping motivated?
I mean, a lot of people
tell me I should retire.
You know, and give it up.
But I got a family, you know.
And there's a lot worse ways
to make a living,
you know, so...
Um, I'm looking forward
to Sunday.
I think it's gonna be
a good one.
STEPHEN QUADROS: So not only
is Mark Coleman here
without the support of
his friend Mark Kerr,
who had to drop out
of his own fight here
-due to health reasons...
-(MEN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
...but he is also
on an uphill battle
against time.
After his recent losses,
you have to ask yourself,
"Is this the end of the road
for Mark Coleman?
"Or will he extend his career
just one more time?"
MAN 1: Turn him around.
But don't strike with him.
That's it!
MAN 2: Going good.
MAN 1: Don't strike.
MAN 2: Now!
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
MAN 1:
Shoot! Take him down!
Yeah! That's what
I'm talking about!
MAN 2: You got him.
MAN 3: Smash him, Thor!
MAN 4: Tear him down!
MAN 1: Pound him!
Pound him! Come on.
Pass the guard!
-Come on, pass that guard.
-MAN 2: Add the pressure.
MAN 5: Hit him! Yes!
MAN 6: There we go! Come on!
MAN 1: Come on! Hit him again.
Pass that guard!
MAN 2: That's it, that's it,
that's it.
MAN 1: Come on! Don't stop!
Don't stop!
-MAN 3: That's it! Yes!
-(BELL RINGING)
STEPHEN QUADROS:
Coleman has done it!
He has won here
at Pride 8 championship
over Ricardo Morais,
breathing new life
into his career.
He clearly has worked
long and hard
to get back in this place
and mindset.
(AUTOMATED GATE WHIRRING)
MARK: Never looked
more beautiful.
DAWN: You look
so beautiful, baby.
I missed you so much, baby.
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MARK: (LAUGHS) Come on!
DAWN: Mmm.
The Gravitron! Look!
I love the Gravitron. So good.
-No?
-Well...
Let's do it. Let's do it.
This is the best.
There's no way
I can ride that.
DAWN: Why? Why?
Why? Because of my tummy.
You know what that
would do to my tummy.
I would get sick everywhere.
-I can't do that.
-No, no.
No, it's about
perspective, okay?
On the inside,
you don't feel it.
It's like you're not moving.
You're, like,
pinned against the wall and...
You're gonna love it.
Does it move on the inside?
It moves,
but it's moving so fast
that you can't even feel it.
Hey, I really wanna go
on the ride with her,
but I have
a sensitive stomach.
Is there... Is there...
The center part in there,
that's the thing that
stays still, right?
Can I stand in there?
In the middle part?
-In the center part?
-MARK: Yes.
No, man, that would be
a serious liability issue.
Uh, well, where would you
recommend I stand then?
'Cause I don't wanna
get sick on the ride,
but I do wanna ride with her.
You don't wanna
get sick on the ride?
I would suggest
you don't go on the ride
if you can't handle it.
Well, it's not that
I can't handle it,
it's just I'm choosing
not to go on it.
Okay, I'm gonna
go on the ride.
You're gonna hold my cake.
-You can hold my bag.
-MARK: Okay.
-Okay? Wish me luck.
-Okay. Thank you.
-MARK: Have fun.
(JUST ANOTHER DAY
BY JON SECADA PLAYING)
(BELL RINGING)
(GRAVITRON WHIRRING)
(THUDDING)
(JUST ANOTHER DAY
BY JON SECADA PLAYING LOUDLY)
(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
-MARK: Here I come!
-You look so cool!
You look so cool!
MARK: I feel so cool.
-This is my speed, baby.
-DAWN: Okay.
This is my speed.
(CHEERFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
COMMENTATOR: Let's go, Rambo!
The drivers are
circling together.
Come on, 45!
COMMENTATOR: Andy Garcia is
still in this.
-Oh!
-COMMENTATOR: Andy Garcia!
Here comes...
ALL: Oh!
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
-Oh!
-COMMENTATOR: Great hit!
Not giving up just yet.
Oh, I think that
back wheel has had it.
DAWN: Yes!
COMMENTATOR: He's good.
He's gotta
find a way out of this,
because they just keep
hitting him in the same spot.
-Whoo-hoo!
-COMMENTATOR: Oh, here we go!
Oh, getting flattened now!
Full speed ahead!
-(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
-COMMENTATOR: Oh!
Madden does another hard hit.
Checking on 50.
The Kenney boys are still
in the mix here
and still moving around.
-(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
-He's okay!
(CLAPPING)
-Whoo!
-He's okay!
COMMENTATOR: Rick's car is
hit the hardest...
MARK: Dawn, what happened
with this over here?
-What do you mean?
-I asked you to
prune the bottom
so the tops will get bigger.
I wanted this to look like
the Road Runner cartoon.
It's just a little nub
of a thing. Just cut it off.
Well, that's not
the way it works.
Right now, it steals water,
and then it ruins
the integrity
from the larger arms.
Well, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
it was such a big deal.
It's just...
It's just a plant. (LAUGHS)
It's not just a plant.
That's a saguaro cactus.
They're hard
to grow like that.
Can I have that knife?
You'd make
a really great father,
you know that?
That's very nice of you
to say and I mean it, but...
It's true.
Well, thank you,
but I'm just not ready,
and I don't know why
you keep bringing that up,
by the way.
It's like you keep forcing it.
I'm not forcing it.
I was just saying,
you have great qualities
and you'd make a great dad,
that's all.
-Why'd you bring it up?
-To be nice.
Well, it's not nice,
because you keep
making me say no.
You already know
how I feel about that.
Look, I love kids...
(SIGHS)
...but I'm always gone,
my mind is preoccupied
with everything else
that's going on,
and you keep bringing this up
about having kids.
I mean, I don't know
what you want me to do.
I look around.
I'm already doing
everything already.
-That's not true, Mark.
-It is true.
I'm already doing
everything around here.
You don't understand.
I just don't have
the mental space
to have a kid.
And... And I'm sorry.
I don't like telling you no.
I was just trying to be nice.
-I know, I know.
-Okay.
And it's very nice.
And... And I appreciate it.
It's just not the right time.
Okay.
Really, Dawn? Look at
all the leaves in the pool.
Are you kidding me, Mark?
It's... That was this morning.
I know, but...
I'll do it.
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
So, how has it been?
It's been really
fucking annoying,
to be honest with you.
It's just...
He's on this
whole high-horse schtick
and I thought
I could handle it,
and I don't know if I can,
because it's like being
with a completely different
fucking person now.
You know how it is
when people get sober,
it's all they can
talk about, so...
(SCOFFS) When he was using,
he was like tender and sweet
and he relied upon me,
and now it's like
he's distant.
It's hard, it's hard to know,
and he's like shitty,
and picking on me, and...
(SIGHS) Well...
I think I miss
taking care of him, you know.
-JACQUELINE: Yeah.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-What? Oh, brain freeze?
-(EXCLAIMING)
Put your tongue
on the roof of your mouth.
-Mmm-mmm.
-It does. Yeah. It works.
-You gotta warm it up.
-It never works. Never.
-I don't know what to do.
-Okay. Here, chug this.
Oh, my God.
JACQUELINE: Okay.
SERVER AND DAWN:
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday,
dear Jacqueline♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
(CHUCKLING)
Thank you. I fuckin' hate you.
-(DAWN CACKLING)
-I'm gonna kill you.
SERVER: Enjoy.
DAWN AND JAQUELINE: Thank you!
DAWN: Just remind me
never to go
back to that place.
That place was the worst.
I feel like I need that pizza.
Sorry.
-Four. Wow.
-Yep.
It's a guarantee
I won't get a headache,
and I can kind of feel it.
Yep. That makes
a lot of sense.
DAWN: Yeah, I thought so.
That's why I said it.
You know,
I'm just out of rehab, Dawn.
-Oh, please. Really?
-I mean, come on.
It's like, I didn't do it
in front of you.
I know, but you're just not
being nice to me right now.
You're not being
very nice to me.
What does that even mean?
I didn't do anything.
-No, you're just...
-I haven't done anything.
...kind of judgy,
and, like, you just got
your shit together
for 21 days, like...
It doesn't make you
any better than me.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it
in that way.
Mark. It's...
It's just 'cause you've got
a problem with something,
it doesn't mean that
everyone in the world
has the same problem
that you do. Okay?
-So just give me a break.
-You wouldn't understand.
Who are you calling?
(MARK EXHALES DEEPLY)
-JEFF: (ON PHONE) Hello.
-Hey, Jeff, it's me.
Oh, it's your sponsor. Okay.
You know what?
You're no fun anymore.
And you're just
a fucking tattletale bitch.
-Hold on. Hold on one second.
-Are you telling on me?
-I'm not telling on you.
-What are you doing?
This is the most difficult
time of my life, Dawn.
Please, please.
I need you to understand.
-I do understand.
-Please.
No, I do. I understand.
But then you go and call Jeff,
and then you just shut me out.
And it really hurts
my feelings,
and I'm here
to talk to you, okay?
But you just gotta let me in.
You don't need Jeff.
Hang up. Hang up.
This is what
I'm talking about.
I mean, this up and down.
I don't know
who I'm talking to.
How the fuck can you say that?
Your behavior is just
so unhealthy for me right now.
Please, Dawn.
You know what? Fuck you, Mark.
Just go fuck yourself.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Jeff, can you hear
what I'm dealing with now?
It's so uncomfortable
in my own home.
I don't know if you had
a chance to hear
what she was saying
when she was screaming.
JEFF: I heard...
MARK: Yeah.
You know what it is?
Is that you're
fucking jealous
that I can still go out
and get drinks
with my friends,
and it's completely fine.
And you wish
you could do that.
Well, stop trying to pretend
that I'm the one
with the fucking problem.
MARK: Did you hear that?
JEFF: Yeah.
-MARK: Yeah, that's her.
-(OBJECTS CLANKING)
I hope you and Jeff...
are real fucking
happy together.
MARK: And she just... I...
I'm gonna call you back.
-All right, thanks, Jeff.
-JEFF: Yeah, okay.
Hey, Dawn?
Dawn?
PRIDE DIRECTOR:
Today, we are happy to have
our greatest fighters
in one room together
for this press conference.
Please give a round of
applause for them.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
We will be holding
a tournament over two events,
leading to
a championship fight
that will result
in the number one fighter
in all of the world.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
And also, we regret
that we disappointed the fans
last time with the cancelation
of the main card
of Enson Inoue
versus Mark Kerr.
We have received Mark's word
that this will not
happen again.
And he has asked
for some time
to address his Japanese fans
regarding his inclusion
in this special tournament.
Hello.
And thank you to everyone
for allowing me
to be here today.
I'd like to apologize,
first and foremost,
to the Pride organization
and staff.
You have been
extremely understanding to me
during my time of dealing
with my personal struggles,
and finally to
the Japanese people,
the Japanese fans.
I know that
you've been questioning
whether I am the fighter
that you thought that I was.
And one of
my biggest regrets in life
is the answer
to that question.
I wasn't.
And I'm ashamed about that.
But I promise you,
that I'm gonna work
even harder
to make this up to you.
Thank you. Arigato.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
(INAUDIBLE)
-Look what the cat dragged in.
-(MARK CHUCKLING)
-Marquito!
-Basito.
-(LAUGHS) What's up, brother?
-Brother.
-Man, good to see you.
-Mwah.
Ooh! I guess we got
some work to do.
-A little bit.
-I'm just kidding, man.
-Yeah, take a look at this.
-BAS: What do you got?
MARK: It's the rules.
BAS: Oof!
Man, they've taken
all your weapons away.
Yeah. Took everything away.
I mean, Coleman's been working
on his striking
and his kicking.
Promoters told him
that they don't want to see
any more grappling
and wrestling.
BAS: Yeah, they wanna see
knockouts.
They want to see people
get knocked out.
Well, look how
he beat Ricardo.
Knocked him out, right?
I mean...
And Enson next year
is gonna do exactly
-the same thing to you.
-Yeah.
He's gonna come for you,
and he wants to knock you out.
You're just gonna
move backwards,
wait for the right moment,
shoot in, take his ass down,
and then you just hit him
in the face, I guess.
-So, no striking?
-No, no striking.
Well, you need
to know striking
in order to get him to tire
to take him to the ground.
But, come on, man,
you know his game plan, right?
Five wins by knockout,
five wins by submission.
And then, last year,
on my freaking birthday,
who won the Abu Dhabi
Combat Club
world championship?
You did.
He's not gonna take you down.
He saw you beat
four amazing grapplers.
Nobody came even close
to submitting you.
So trust me,
this guy is not gonna take you
to the ground.
-Thank you.
-You ready?
-I think so.
-You think so?
Come on, Mark,
it's a yes or no answer.
(MOCKINGLY) "I think so."
(IN NORMAL VOICE) That's
right. Come on. Are you ready?
-Yes.
-Oh! Looky.
Look at the sight of the show.
-Marquito... is back.
-(BELL RINGING)
(ALARM RINGING)
Uh, actually, we're gonna
have to wait ten seconds...
(CHUCKLING)
...till the buzzer goes.
So, deep breaths.
(EXHALES)
-(ALARM BEEPING)
-Okay, here we go. Two.
Good. Again.
-Four.
-(MARK GRUNTING)
Good. Uppercut straight.
Nice.
Very good.
Good. Now switch. Boom!
There we go. You see.
Stop playing with that.
BAS: How do you feel?
(CHUCKLES) Good.
That's how you should feel.
(MARK GRUNTING)
Okay. Okay.
Mark, Mark, Mark, watch.
You're looking where
you're gonna hit, right?
I went to hit you in the head,
well, you're gonna defend it.
Now, so what I do,
I hit the body
and I hit it hard
because he needs to defend it.
He needs to respect it.
Boom to the body,
boom to the body.
Same motto. Boom to the head.
But you see,
you don't look at the head.
All right?
So you hit here, boom!
And you go...
(BAS GROANS,
BREATHING THROUGH TEETH)
-MARK: Bas?
-(BAS SOBS)
MARK: Bas, you okay?
-He's having a heart attack.
-BAS: No, no, no.
MARK: Someone call
911 right now.
BAS: No, no, no.
It's my freakin' tendon, dude.
-Did you tear it?
-BAS: My ten... No!
It's messed up my career.
-(GROANS)
-You okay?
BAS: No, it's freaking...
It's going to go off
for an hour and a half.
I know this.
I've been here many times.
Shit!
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(BAS BREATHING SHARPLY)
BAS: Okay. We need to get
something, guys.
I think... One is coming.
I need to go to a hospital
or something.
MAN: Breathe, breathe.
Breathe, breathe.
(BAS BREATHING SHAKILY)
Oh, and it's gonna be
an hour and a half.
I know this is gonna be
-MAN: Breathe.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's wrong with this one?
Oh, dude.
-Ow!
-Okay. Okay. Which one?
Which one? Which one?
-BAS: It's this arm.
-This one?
-Yeah.
-MARK: Okay.
I'm not using.
I swear to God, I'm clean.
-This is old.
-I don't give a shit.
Do anything.
I don't give a shit.
MARK: Okay.
(BAS GRUNTS)
(EXHALING)
Five seconds, all your pain is
gonna go away.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh.
Oh. (EXHALING)
-Just breathe.
-BAS: Yeah, that's good.
Oh, dude...
Oh, dude,
I feel like a plant.
(CHUCKLES) That's it.
How do you fight
on that shit?
You just get used to it.
Wow.
Wow, man, that's hot.
-(EXHALES)
-Just breathe.
Now I know why
you were always sweaty.
You were always sweaty.
-Ooh. This is weird.
-Just breathe. Just breathe.
BAS: Oh.
Oh, man.
Different world.
(MY WAY
BY FRANK SINATRA PLAYING)
BAS: Yes!
Yes!
Okay. Go around.
(CHUCKLING)
BAS: Yes!
Yes!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Come on.
-Double cross.
-(BOTH GRUNTING)
BAS: Good! Take a breather.
(MARK EXHALES)
(GRUNTING)
STEPHEN QUADROS: Hi,
everybody, and welcome to
the Pride Grand Prix 2000
opening round.
Tonight we have
16 men competing
in eight different fights.
One clash
I'm really excited about
is the clash
between Mark Kerr
and Enson Inoue.
Wrestling versus jiu-jitsu.
That's gonna be
a great one, Bas.
It's gonna be
a super exciting fight
and I'll tell you why.
Because last time,
Mark Kerr wasn't
in the best shape.
This time, though,
he came back to me.
And you know as well as I do,
once you acquire the skill set
of mixed martial arts,
I think that endurance
is the most important aspect
of mixed martial arts.
So he can go the distance.
Let's hope so.
Uh, one thing everybody's been
talking about is
the potential collision
between the two Americans
in this tournament.
Bas, have you spoken
to either Kerr or Coleman
about the thought
of fighting such a good friend
for a life-changing
amount of money?
That's
a super intense question,
Stephen, and, no, I have not.
But I can only imagine
they're deep
in each other's heads
right now.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING
FAINTLY ON SPEAKERS)
(CHUCKLES)
-Coleman, you see this?
-COLEMAN: Yeah?
What page?
MARK: Seven.
(CHUCKLES)
Caught you mid-breath.
Yeah, I look exhausted.
MARK: You look
good though, man.
COLEMAN: Yeah.
All right, go to five.
Look at that.
That's a great one mid-kick.
(CHUCKLES)
Coleman, you wanna
have some fun?
What do you mean?
Come on.
COLEMAN: Yeah?
MARK: Yeah.
(CARS HONKING HORNS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Wow.
-It's fuckin' cool, man.
-Oh, yeah.
Lot of people.
They love you, man.
They're not...
Come on, go say hi to 'em.
Come on, bro, come on.
(CROWD CONTINUES CHEERING)
(FANS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(ELECTRIC GUITAR
PLAYING KIMIGAYO)
(ALL MOUTHING)
(PLAYING HIGH-PITCHED RIFF)
STEPHEN QUADROS: That was
Tomoyasu Hotei
with an incredible rendition
of the Japanese
national anthem
to welcome us all
to the first round of
the Pride 2000 Grand Prix
tournament.
This is the first round
of the two-round Grand Prix
to crown the greatest fighter
in the world.
I gotta say, it's so great
to see Mark Kerr
back out there
smiling amongst
this highly-elite
group of fighters.
Please rise
for The Star-Spangled Banner.
(SINGING THE STAR-SPANGLED
BANNER)
ANNOUNCER: Mark Coleman!
STEPHEN QUADROS: Mark Coleman
is really excited
to be back here,
saying he has trained
as hard as he possibly could
with the hopes that
he can continue his ride here
at the top of this sport.
If he wins this fight,
he'll secure a spot
in the final round
of this Grand Prix,
and keep his hope alive
for the $200,000 grand prize.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
CORNERMAN:
You got him! You got him!
That's it! That's it!
Keep it up. Keep it up.
STEPHEN QUADROS: And that is
the neck crack.
And there's the tap
from Satake.
A huge victory
for Mark Coleman
as he secures his spot
in the finals of
the Pride 2000 Grand Prix.
Look at that rare show
of emotion
as he climbs the ropes.
Next up is Mr. "Ice Cold"
Igor Vovchanchyn,
as he looks to move
on to the finals of
the Pride 2000 Grand Prix.
(BELL RINGING)
STEPHEN QUADROS:
And there it is,
another decisive victory
from Igor Vovchanchyn
as he moves on to
the final round.
(ANNOUNCER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
STEPHEN QUADROS: Another
promising Japanese fighter
has made it
past the first round of
this tournament
and into the finals.
ANNOUNCER: Enson Inoue!
STEPHEN QUADROS:
Enson Inoue has carved
into the back of his head
the Japanese character
for "Death." (CHUCKLES)
Something tells me
he's not too happy with Kerr
for having to drop out
of their fight in Pride 8
back in November of last year.
ANNOUNCER: Mark Kerr!
(CROWD CHEERING)
STEPHEN QUADROS: I got to say,
to see Mark back out there
after everything
he's been through
is truly remarkable,
and we should all commend him
for such a turn-around.
But this is
his first real test
against the dangerous
and promising new fighter,
Enson Inoue.
And I can't help
but ask myself,
does Mark Kerr
still have it in him?
Can he still fight
with everything
he's been through?
I guess we'll find out
the answer to that question
very soon.
Mark, I'm gonna bring you
into the center of the ring
for the final instruction.
That's it. You ready?
Mark, you ready?
-Let's fight.
-(BELL RINGS)
Okay, take your time.
You got time enough.
Yes! Yes!
All right, Mark,
start kicking his legs.
Let's go. Let's go.
Yes! Nice job.
Slow it down. Relax.
Just keep kicking
those legs, buddy.
Oh, there we go! Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Just kick him.
REFEREE: Down, down, down.
Stand up.
You're out, you're out.
Fight!
BAS: Nice!
Good job, brother.
Yes, here we go.
Okay, take his ass out. Yes!
The last one of these. Do it!
Yes, Mark!
Yeah, Mark, keep going!
-(EXCLAIMS) Yes!
-Hey, man, call it, call it.
(BELL RINGS)
STEPHEN QUADROS:
Kerr has done it.
He has come back
from the brink
to win a place in the finals
of the 2000 Pride Grand Prix.
Yeah!
Not only has
he kept himself in the running
for the $200,000
cash grand prize,
but he's also proven
that he still has it in him,
and he's someone
who could really win
this whole tournament.
That was
a vengeance performance
from Kerr, and he and Bas
should be extremely proud
of that one.
There he is, Mark Kerr.
(CROWD CHEERING)
STEPHEN QUADROS: All those
fighters you see in the ring
will go into the finals
on May 1, 2000.
The winner of
the tournament walks away
with a whopping $200,000.
Life-changing money.
Now that's no chump change.
You know it's gonna be
you and me, right?
It's gonna happen,
man, me and you. (CHUCKLES)
We always said
we couldn't turn it down.
For 200 grand,
I'm gonna whoop your ass.
I don't wanna have to
mess you up.
Bring it. I'm ready.
-Let's have fun.
-All right.
COLEMAN: I fucking love you.
I love you, man.
COLEMAN: Make the most
out of it, all right?
It is what it is
until it isn't.
COLEMAN: Yeah.
-How wild is this?
-Crazy.
(MEN GRUNTING)
-MARK: Dude.
-Nice.
MARK: Go for it.
Okay, I wanted to
bring you something, okay.
-What is it?
-It's a present.
-(CHUCKLES) Open it, dummy.
-(MARK CHUCKLES)
DAWN: Do you remember
this guy?
So I've been reading
about Japan,
and there's this, um,
Japanese theory,
and it's called like
a kint... kintsugi...
-Yeah, I heard of that.
-(LAUGHS) Kintsugi, or some...
Whatever. They say
when you repair something,
it makes it more, um,
beautiful and more meaningful
due to the history and...
It has some history,
so I just wanted to fix it.
And, I don't know,
it's like you're supposed to
use gold to...
(LAUGHS) But I had Krazy Glue
so I used Krazy Glue instead.
MARK: You Krazy-Glued this?
DAWN: I Krazy-Glued it. Yeah.
-Piece by piece.
-Oh, my God!
I think it's the point that
it's supposed to look
-kind of bad.
-MARK: No, no, no.
-It doesn't look bad.
-DAWN: It's kind of bad.
-DAWN: Mmm-hmm.
-It's beautiful.
-Yeah?
It's the most meaningful thing
anyone's ever done.
And I love you.
You happy, baby?
You're so sweaty. Oh, God.
-BAS: Come on, buddy.
-No, no, no.
BAS: Let's go. Next round.
-Chop, chop. Ding, ding, ding.
-MARK: Yeah.
BAS: Come on, Mark.
MARK: Yeah.
So tomorrow, what was it?
Tomorrow I figured
I'd work out
for about an hour or so
back at the hotel,
and then we'll hit the road,
drive back to Phoenix.
So, what are you
gonna do next week?
With who?
Who's gonna do it for you?
I'll figure it out.
Listen, you really believe
this is a good idea?
Yeah, I know what
I'm doing, all right?
Okay.
You ready, baby?
-Yeah. Time to go?
-Yeah.
Yeah. I'm gonna pull
the car up, okay?
All right.
DAWN: You ready, baby?
MARK: I'm ready, baby.
-MARK: Hey, Dawn?
-Yeah.
(WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY)
What do you think?
Where'd my baby go?
-(CHUCKLES) He's right here.
-(DAWN CHUCKLES)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(BOTH PANTING)
-Good job, buddy. Good job.
(EXHALES)
(UPBEAT SONG PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
Honey, why is
Coleman calling you?
-Did you call him?
-Mmm-mmm.
He's probably just calling to
check up on me.
Bas also called you,
which I thought was
kind of weird.
(CHUCKLES) It's not weird.
They're my friends.
I just thought it was funny
that they're both calling you.
Well, it's not...
They're my friends.
It's perfectly normal
for them to call me,
just to check up on me.
They just called you
out of the blue?
Dawn, I have a big fight
in a couple of weeks.
They're probably just calling
to see how I feel about it.
(CHUCKLES, CLEARS THROAT)
Makes sense.
So they weren't calling
to make sure you wouldn't cave
and bring me
to Japan with you?
You listened to
my answering machine?
Yeah, I did.
I did because I'm not hearing
shit from you.
So, do you agree with them?
What are you
talking about, Dawn?
Say it. That you don't want me
to go with you to Japan.
-I'm not gonna say that, Dawn.
-Why? Just say it.
I'm just... I just need, like,
a couple of days. That's it.
I just need two days.
That's it.
Just to focus.
You're saying
I can't help you focus?
No, I'm not saying
that at all.
I'm just saying, Dawn,
I need you to understand,
this is a big deal for me.
It's the biggest fight ever.
I just need a couple of days.
That's it.
Just a couple of days
to focus.
Bas is saying I just need it
-without any distractions.
-I got it, I got it, I got it.
You know what?
I don't fucking get it.
-What don't you get, Dawn?
-I don't fucking get it
because I do everything
for you around here, okay?
I book your appointments,
I cook for you,
I clean your
fucking underwear.
-I know you do.
-And I'm
-the big fucking distraction?
-No, you're not.
I've thanked you in the past,
and I appreciate
everything you do.
This is a crazy tournament.
This is the biggest fight
of my life.
Just say
you don't want me to go.
I'm not gonna say that to you.
It confuses the situation.
Yeah, I want you to say it
to me. There's nothing
-confusing about it.
-I'm not gonna say that.
You just look me in the eye
and you tell me you hate me,
-and you don't want me to go.
-What the fuck are you...
I'm not gonna say that.
And how many times
do I have to rewrite
-my boundaries with you?
-I don't want you to
-rewrite...
-This is so fucking
-exhausting. Please, Dawn.
-I'm sorry, I just...
Mark, I just need you
to let me in.
I feel so excluded
from everything.
And I'd love to know
about your fighting.
about your training,
how you're feeling
in your body,
but you don't want to tell me.
-Holy shit!
-Dawn, don't do that.
Do not do that.
Don't act like all of a sudden
you give two shits
about my body and my training,
when the only thing
you care about is yourself.
Really?
Inserting yourself
into everything.
Yes, that's it.
Always about you.
Only about fucking you.
Because everything is about...
-You!
And all you give me
are your
shitty fucking leftovers,
and you keep telling me
it's dinnertime.
That's good.
You read that in one of
your little fucking books?
Fuck you, asshole.
Yeah, I did,
and it's how I feel.
It's how you feel.
You wanna know how I feel?
You know what sucks
and what's not nice
is that I'm working my ass off
trying to stay
sober around here.
(SCOFFS) Sure, okay.
Yeah, maybe
I'll call your sponsor.
Don't fucking do that.
You stop!
Don't fucking work
my program like that.
-Don't you fucking work...
-Don't you fucking get...
-... my program like that.
-...in my face.
You want to hit me?
Let's go. Come on.
Let's fucking go.
Mr... Mr. Fucking in Control.
I don't know what to do.
I'm working my ass off
to make a life-changing
amount of money.
And what are you doing?
I just get out of rehab
and you're out till
four o'clock
in the morning
with your friends.
You're drinking.
You're eating Advil
at fucking 2:30
in the afternoon.
You think that's nice to me?
You think that's encouraging?
No, it's rude and it's selfish
and it's fucked up,
and that's why
you're not going to Japan.
DAWN: I knew it was you.
I knew it was
your fucking idea.
You knew it?
Yeah, of course you did.
Of course.
Because it's all about you.
-All about you.
-But you don't care about me.
You don't care
about my feelings.
You just care about yourself
and your dumb fucking friends
and your
stupid fucking fighting.
My stupid fucking fighting
that's paid
for this fucking house.
My stupid fucking fighting
that's paid for the car.
Paid for that fucking outfit.
But that's
how you like it, Mark.
-Yes, and by the way...
-You just want to...
-...that's on you.
-...control everything.
That's on you.
All these insecurities, Dawn,
are on you.
So whatever's going on
in that fucked up head
of yours,
that's an inside job.
I don't think you know
a damn thing about me.
You don't know
You know that, Mark?
I think it's best
if you leave.
We're having a party.
-Cancel the party.
-No.
Because everybody's
coming over
and everyone's excited.
And I was
really excited about it.
And I feel like we could just
talk about this tomorrow.
And I don't have to come
to Japan or anything.
It's okay.
Dawn, go in the room,
pack a bag,
and get out.
(JUNGLELAND
BY BRUCE SPRINGSTEEN PLAYING)
(KEYPAD ON SAFE BEEPING)
(DAWN SOBS)
Dawn.
Dawn. Dawn.
Dawn, no. Dawn, no! No!
(GRUNTS) Get off me!
(CRYING)
Dawn. Dawn, open the door.
Baby, we're gonna talk
this through.
I need you to look me
in the eyes
just so you can see
what I'm feeling.
-Dawn.
-(LID POPS)
(PILLS CLATTERING)
Stop! Get your
fucking hands off me!
Get your fucking hands
off me, Mark!
I wasn't gonna do anything!
I was just pretending,
Mark, I promise.
You're fucking hurting me,
Mark, please.
I'm not gonna let you go.
-I fucking...
-(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
I fucking hate you!
I fucking hate you, Mark!
I've wasted
my whole fucking life on you.
(VOICE BREAKS)
Look what you do to me!
-(SOBS)
-(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
Mark...
Get your fucking hands
off me, Mark!
I'm not letting go. I'm not...
I'm not letting go. (EXHALES)
POLICE OFFICER:
We're not going to arrest,
but we will take you
to see a doctor.
Okay? The doctor's gonna
assess her in the ER.
And will I be able to see her?
You'll be able to see her,
but after a medical doctor
actually comes in
and assesses her first.
(JUNGLELAND CONTINUES PLAYING)
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
Which fighter would you
like to win the next round?
Fujita or Mark Kerr?
Yeah, that's
a very difficult question.
I don't think
I can answer that one.
JOURNALIST:
I totally understand.
Let's say what if
Mark Kerr does win?
Would it be hard
for you to fight
such a good friend of yours?
Yeah, of course. But look,
if it happens,
it happens, right?
I'm gonna give it my all.
He's gonna do the same.
And we'll see what happens.
-JOURNALIST: Okay.
-Okay.
Thank you very much.
-Yes, sir. Thank you.
-Good luck.
Appreciate it.
ANNOUNCER: Mark Coleman!
STEPHEN QUADROS:
Mark Coleman enters
the finals off the heels
of a decisive victory
against Satake
in the first round.
Given his recent losses
before that match,
this could be Coleman's
last chance
at this elusive championship.
He has a tough round...
All right, Mark,
Coleman's about to get up.
Come on, watch.
STEPHEN QUADROS:
A promising fighter looking to
make a name for himself.
But a victory here tonight
would pit him
against the winner of
Kerr versus Fujita
later this evening.
Coleman's trainer has told us
that he has been working
on his boxing game recently
and that we should, quote,
"Watch out for some KOs."
CORNERMAN 1:
Come on, Coleman. Hands up.
CORNERMAN 2:
Watch it, watch it. Yeah.
Take him down! Take him down!
CORNERMAN 1: Body lock.
Body lock, yes!
CORNERMAN 2: Come on! Come on!
Mark! No, no, no!
Get back up! Get up! Get up!
That's it. That's it. Jab.
CORNERMAN 1: Yes!
Yes! Yes!
(CROWD CHEERING ON TV)
(SPEAKING UKRAINIAN)
CORNERMAN 2: (IN ENGLISH)
Mark, come on.
CORNERMAN 1: Watch his foot.
Take him down. Hit it.
Finish him.
CORNERMAN 2:
Take him down! Take him down!
Yes! Yes!
Man, Coleman can fucking hit.
CORNERMAN 2:
That's it. Again! Again!
-Again!
-CORNERMAN 1: Yes!
CORNERMAN 2: Yes! Yes!
CORNERMAN 1: Yes!
CORNERMAN 2: You got him!
CORNERMAN 2:
He's going, he's going.
-(BELL RINGING)
-STEPHEN QUADROS: That is it!
Mark Coleman virtually put
a beating on Akira Shoji
and the judges have
to have seen that.
CORNERMAN 1: Yes!
STEPHEN QUADROS:
And there you have it, folks.
It's a unanimous decision win
for Mark "The Hammer" Coleman.
It was a dominant
one-sided victory
that brings him
one step closer
to the grand prize.
Coleman will await
the winner of the fight
between Kazuyuki Fujita
and his good friend,
Mark Kerr.
(MARK EXHALES)
All right. Let's go.
STEPHEN QUADROS:
Kazuyuki Fujita presents
a tough,
tough challenge for Kerr
as he is one of the best
heavyweights in the division.
A win here would cement
Fujita's place in history.
From the looks on his face
and his attitude,
Fujita appears to be a man
on a mission,
and something tells me
it might take
a wrecking ball to stop him.
Kerr is fresh off
his miraculous win
over Enson Inoue
in the first round,
and he looks to keep
his good fortune going
with a win against
one of the toughest fighters
in the division.
Will Kerr silence
his critics here with a win?
Or will all his hopes
and dreams come crashing down?
If Kerr is in any way
similar to the man
I know he is,
he will want to win this fight
and tournament
more than life itself.
(THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING)
All right. Ready? Fight.
Close the bars. Nice job.
Nice jabs on him.
(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
Nice! Good job!
Yes! Nice!
Don't stop. Go push in.
Oh, jeez!
Yes! Get him back.
Yes! You got him back.
Let's go, let's go.
(FUJITA'S CORNERMAN
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
That's illegal.
Mark, get out
of this situation.
Just get up, man.
Yes, take your time.
Take your time.
Move around. Take a breath.
(THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES)
-(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
-Come on, Mark.
BAS: (EXCLAIMS) Nice one.
Yeah! Uh-oh.
Nice job!
Nice! Oy!
Good job, good job.
Take your time. Relax.
Breathe in.
Take that takedown.
Come on, Mark.
Get up.
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Mark!
You got to improve
your position, Mark.
Come on!
Lower your back so you can
see him coming at least.
Get up, Mark.
Watch out for his knees.
Improve your position.
Come on, Mark! Come on.
-(MARK GRUNTS)
-(BELL RINGING)
STEPHEN QUADROS: Oh, my
goodness! Kerr has lost.
He is out of the tournament.
This has to be the first
major upset of the evening.
I have no idea what happened
to Mark out there.
He just couldn't move.
This is truly shocking.
All right. Get up, Mark.
STEPHEN QUADROS: One thing
I have to call attention to
is Mark's heart,
because we have seen a lot
of tap outs
in this tournament.
But Mark fell on his sword
in front of these
thousands of fans.
And for them,
he would rather be beaten
than quit.
I can tell you from experience
-that takes a true champion.
-BAS: Don't worry about it.
I still love you, brother.
STEPHEN QUADROS: Fujita moves
on to fight Mark Coleman
for a place in the final fight
of the evening
as we await the winner
of the Vovchanchyn
versus Sakuraba fight
and we get closer
to that $200,000 grand prize.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
Can we turn
the lights out, Bas?
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
I'm going to get you
some ice, too. Okay?
Yeah.
Hey, Mark.
Come here, big guy.
BAS: Raja, where
can I find some ice?
Over there.
How you doing, Mark?
BAS: All right, keep
your eyes closed
and put this on it.
Try to relax, all right?
(EXHALES)
-Mark, can you hear me?
-Yeah.
DR. CORTEZ: Do you know
what happened to you?
-Yeah, I lost.
-Yeah, you did.
Do you know
where you are right now?
-Japan.
-DR. CORTEZ: Good.
Do I need stitches?
Yeah, you need a few stitches.
-MARK: Is it bad?
-No, it's not horrible.
I'm just gonna go over here
and get everything ready.
All right? It'll be
a few minutes.
You just sit tight here.
-MARK: Yeah, okay.
-All right.
I could not move my body.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
It's like I...
It was like I was dead.
Yep, I've been there, buddy.
I couldn't move.
Listen, Mark,
I hate to do this, brother,
but I gotta go back
to the commentary table, okay?
I gotta work.
-Okay.
-BAS: All right, man.
Bas, thank you.
Thank you for everything.
-BAS: You're welcome, brother.
-Yes.
-I'm sorry.
-BAS: No, no, no.
Don't say that.
-You got him?
-I got him.
BAS: All right. Sounds good.
Hey, Doc.
Doc, sorry.
-Hey, Mark.
-How's Kerr?
He's okay. He's all right.
He got a gash here.
We gotta stitch that up.
How's his head?
-It's clearing up.
-Does he care if I go in?
-No, no, go in. Go in.
-Coleman.
COLEMAN: Thank you.
What's going on, bud?
MARK: Hey, man.
-How you feeling?
-(SIGHS) You know.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm a little banged up.
Nothing to worry
about, though.
Whatever. Let it go.
It happens.
It's one night.
We've all been there.
You heard about Fujita, right?
He's out.
He's not coming back.
He's injured.
Yeah, I know, I know.
It's all yours
to win now, Cole.
-For real?
-For real.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Yeah, buddy, it's all yours.
Go get it.
I'll fucking get it.
-MARK: It's all yours.
-Appreciate that.
-I love you, buddy.
-I love you.
-Go bring it home.
-I'll get it done.
STEPHEN QUADROS:
So Mark Coleman is coming
into this final
looking fresh as ever
after his good friend,
Mark Kerr,
inadvertently did him a favor
after Fujita injured his knee
in their fight together.
The question is,
will Coleman be able
to avenge Kerr
against his nemesis,
Igor Vovchanchyn?
Or will Igor continue
his reign
as the top heavyweight
in the division?
All right, Mark,
I'm gonna tell you
what I'm gonna do
every step of the way.
All right?
You just let me know
if anything is bothering you.
STEPHEN QUADROS:
I should also note
this is the first time
a Pride event
has ever been broadcast
in North America.
And I think
they are in for a real treat.
REFEREE: All right.
(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(BELL RINGS)
(CORNERMAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
You're gonna feel
a little pinch,
and then a lot of burning.
Pinch.
A lot of burning.
CORNERMAN: Take your time!
There you go! Yes!
Come on! Come on! Handle him!
Yes, yes, yes!
Spin him around! Spin him!
DR. CORTEZ: And two more.
CORNERMAN: Keep going!
Keep going!
Yes! Yes!
(IGOR GRUNTS)
STEPHEN QUADROS:
There's the tap.
Wow! Igor has tapped out.
Mark Coleman has won
the Pride 2000 Grand Prix.
Oh! Look at the excitement
in that man.
He's crazy excited,
and he's running to the fans.
-He's running to the fans.
-COLEMAN: Yes!
STEPHEN QUADROS:
He just won $200,000.
DR. CORTEZ:
All right. You're all done.
(CORRIDOR OF DREAMS PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(MARK GRUNTS)
(CORRIDOR OF DREAMS
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(CHUCKLING)
-Hi, how are you?
-CASHIER: Hi.
(JAZZY MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
-CASHIER: How are you?
-I'm good.
-Thank you.
-CASHIER: Good.
-How was your day so far?
-CASHIER: So far, so good.
-Yours?
-It's good.
-CASHIER: Good.
-Gonna get real busy.
-CASHIER: Yeah.
-(LAUGHS)
(MAKE THE WORLD GO AWAY
BY TIMI YURO PLAYING)
Uh... (CHUCKLES)
Unbelievable.
(CHUCKLING)
Uh... Oh, boy.
Amazing.
See you, guys.
(MAKE THE WORLD GO AWAY
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(ENGINE TURNS OVER, WHIRRING)
(SONG ENDS)
(LIMELIGHT BY THE ALAN PARSONS
PROJECT PLAYING)
(HARP MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)